https://web-japan.org/plaza/privacy.html

Others
>>Recent Results of "This Month's Question"
Web Japan Leaflet PDF DOWNLOAD
©  Web Japan,
Web Japan Privacy Policy
1. Basic premise
The Web Japan website ("Site") collects information from users related to areas necessary for the smooth operation of provided services (including but not limited to the provision of information on the Site, acceptance of user questions and comments, the What's New Mail Service, shipment of gifts).
The information acquired will be used appropriately within the scope of the purpose of use as shown below.
2. Scope of information acquisition
(1) The Site automatically collects and stores Internet domain names, IP addresses, OS versions and browser versions from those who access the Site.
(2) We ask users to register their E-mail addresses and names in order to use the "What's New Mail Service" or to make submissions for posting on the "Bulletin Board" page.
(3) We ask users to submit responses to the questionnaire as well as optionally register their name, gender, E-mail address and postal address in the "Questionnaire" page.
(4) When an E-mail message is sent to the Web Master, the sender's E-mail address will be displayed on the recipient's screen.
3. Purpose of use
(1) The information acquired in 2.(1) will be used as reference for the smooth operation of services provided by the Site.
(2) The E-mail addresses acquired in 2.(2) will not be used for purposes other than for sending E-mail notifications as part of the "What's New Mail Service," for posting on the "Bulletin Board" Information pages, and for provision of information related to Web Japan.
(3) The responses to the questionnaire as well as names, gender, postal addresses, E-mail addresses and other information acquired in 2.(3) will not be used for purposes other than for responding to users' questions and comments, shipping gifts, and providing information related to Web Japan. The responses to the questionnaire collected through the "Questionnaire" page will be used as reference for the proper operation of the Site.
(4) The E-mail addresses acquired in 2.(4) will be used only for responding to senders' comments and questions.
4. Limitation on use and provision
Except in cases of legal disclosure requests, cases of illegal access, threats and other unlawful acts or other special reasons, the information acquired by the Site will not be used by ourselves for purposes other than those described in 3., or be disclosed to third parties, provided, however, that statistical information regarding access to the Site or information on user attributes may at times be made public.
5. Disclosure of own personal information
(1) With regard to the personal information registered on the "Bulletin Board" page addressed in 2.(2), one may not request disclosure of his/her own personal information due to the fact that it is difficult for us to verify the identity of the requester as being the owner of that information. With regard to the information on the "What's New Mail Service" page, one can remove or change any part of his/her own personal information as his/her discretion.
6. Scope of application
This privacy policy applies only to this Site.
7. Changes and notices
This Privacy Policy may be changed without prior notice. As we cannot notify users of such changes as they occur, please confirm the latest Privacy Policy on this page from time to time.
8. Disclaimer
- While we make every effort to maintain the accuracy of the information provided by the Site, Web Japan shall assume no responsibility for any actions taken by a user through use of any information contained on this Site.
- Web Japan shall not be liable for any damages, either suffered by a user or inflicted by a user upon a third party, arising from the use of this Site.
